James A. Baker III Papers, 1957-2011 (bulk 1972-1992): Finding Aid MC197
Public Policy Papers
- Series 7: Secretary of the Treasury, 1983-1988; 19 boxes
  - Subseries 7A. Confirmation, 1985; 1 box
    The Confirmation subseries documents the confirmation process related to Baker's nomination as Secretary of the Treasury. Included are transcripts of confirmation hearings, Baker's hearing preparation and study material, and financial disclosure documents.
    - Confirmation Hearing, 1985; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Confirmation Process, 1985; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Financial Disclosure, 1985; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Testimony Study Material, 1985; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 7B. Congressional Appearances, 1985-1988; 1 box
    The Congressional Appearances subseries documents Baker's appearances and testimony before the House and Senate. An index which lists each appearance by date is included at the front of the first folder of the subseries. Documents related to each appearance are preceded by a tab listing the committee name, subject of the testimony, and whether Baker appeared before the House or Senate. The text of Baker's statement is usually included (sometimes in the form of a Treasury news release).
    - 1985-1988, 2 folders (Box 80, Folder 5-6)
  - Subseries 7C. Correspondence, 1983-1988; 9 boxes
    The Correspondence subseries consists of Baker's correspondence files from his tenure as Secretary of the Treasury. Of note are several letters regarding economic policy from economist Jude Wanniski, as well as correspondence from George H. W. Bush, Ronald and Nancy Reagan, Donald T. Regan, Richard Nixon, Pete Wilson, and Senators Phil Gramm and Daniel Patrick Moynihan. Some of the correspondence is brief, as in the case of Strom Thurmond, whose file primarily consists of letters of thanks for gifts of South Carolina fruit and cheese.
    As with the correspondence files in other series, the Treasury correspondence includes correspondence with government officials and staff, as well as family and friends. The largest volume of correspondence, like the correspondence files in the Chief of Staff and Secretary of State files, is from Baker's cousin, Preston Moore, Jr.
    The chronological correspondence grouping consists of Baker's personal correspondence files. It primarily contains outgoing correspondence, both of a personal and professional nature. There is slight, but not significant, overlap between the chronological and alphabetical correspondence files.
    The Correspondence subseries is arranged alphabetically by last name of correspondent, and chronologically within each folder. Personal chronological files are arranged chronologically.
    - Alphabetical Files, 1983-1988; 7 boxes
      - Ahmed, A, 1985; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Alexander, George, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - Alexander, Lamar, 1987; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Allen, Richard V, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - Annenberg, Walter, 1988; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - Archer, Bill, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - Armstrong, Anne, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 13)
      - Arneson, Paul, 1986; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 14)
      - Atherton, Holt, 1985; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 15)
        contains correspondence from George Bush
      - A Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Badham, Robert E, 1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Baker, Howard H, 1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Baldridge, Malcolm, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Barun, Ken, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Bauer, Gary L, 1988; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Bennett, William, 1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - Block, John R, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Boschwitz, Rudy, 1987; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Bostian, David, 1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - Bowen, Otis R, 1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Bradshaw, Thornton F, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - Brady, Nicholas, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - Brock, William E. III, 1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - Brown, Sarah Nash, 1988; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - Buchanan, Patrick, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - Bush, Barbara, 1985; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 17)
      - Bush, George H. W, 1985-1987; 2 folders (Box 81, Folder 18-19)
      - Bush, Prescott S. Jr, 1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 20)
      - Bush, William H. T, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 21)
      - Butler, Michael F, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 22)
      - Byrd, Robert C, 1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 23)
      - B Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 24)
      - Cabaniss, John T, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 25)
      - Cain, Dixon H, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 26)
      - Carlin, Paul N, 1985; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 27)
      - Carter, Jimmy, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 28)
      - Casey, Albert V, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 29)
      - Casey, William J, 1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 30)
      - Chiles, Lawton, 1985; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 31)
      - Christian, Nancy M, 1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 32)
      - Cicconi, James W, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 33)
      - Coe, Douglas E, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 34)
      - Colepaugh, Ceia Webb, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 35)
      - Colgan, Catherine Smyth, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 36)
      - Conable, Barber, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Cone, Clarence D. Jr, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Cooke, Jack Kent, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Cox, Jack, 1985; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Craxi, Bettino, 1985; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Crow, Trammell, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Cuartas, Belisario Betancur, 1985; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Cuomo, Mario M, 1986; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Curtin, John D. Jr, 1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - C Miscellaneous, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - Daniel, Bill, 1985; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Darman, Richard G, 1986; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - DeConcini, Dennis, 1985; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - Dillon, C. Douglas, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - Dingell, John D, undated; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 15)
      - Doha, A. R. Shams-Ud, 1985; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - Dole, Robert, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 17)
      - Domenici, Pete V, 1985; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 18)
      - Duberstein, Kenneth M, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 19)
      - Duncan, John J, undated; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 20)
      - D Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 21)
      - Exon, J. James, 1986; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 22)
      - E Miscellaneous, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 23)
      - Fahrenkopf, Frank J. Jr, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 24)
      - Fanfani, Amintore, 1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 25)
      - Farb, Carolyn, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 26)
      - Fielding, Fred F, 1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 27)
      - Fields, Jack, 1988; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 28)
      - Finger, Jerry E, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 29)
      - Forbes, Malcom S, 1986; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 30)
      - Ford, Gerald R, 1985; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 31)
      - Forse, Don, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 32)
      - Fuller, Parmer, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 33)
      - F Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 34)
      - Gavin, John, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 35)
      - Gillcrist, Dan, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 36)
      - Glenn, Paul F, 1985; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 37)
      - Goodling, William F, 1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 38)
      - Goria, Giovanni Giuseppe, 1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 39)
      - Goss, Bernard, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 40)
      - Gould, George D, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 41)
      - Graham, Billy, 1988; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 42)
      - Gramm, Phil, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 43)
      - Gray, Edwin J, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 44)
      - Gray, William H. III, 1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Green, Bill, 1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Grune, George V, 1985; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - G Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - Hall, Ralph M, 1985; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Halverson, Richard C, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - Harlow, Bryce N, undated; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Hartung, Frank, 1985; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Hartwell, Samuel A, 1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Hawke, R. J. L, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Hawkins, Paula, 1985; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 11)
      - Haynes, Richard D, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - Heinz, John, 1985; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - Henry, Audrey, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - Heyer, George S. Jr, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - Hobbs, Claude E, 1985; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - Hodel, Donald P, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - Holladay, J. Douglas, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - Huller, Allan R, 1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - Hunt, Ray L, 1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - Hwan, Chun Doo, 1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 21)
      - H Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 22)
      - Ireland, Andrew P, 1985; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 23)
      - I Miscellaneous, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 24)
      - Jordan, Hamilton, 1985; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 25)
      - J Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 26)
      - Kampelman, Max M, 1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 27)
      - Kasten, Robert W. Jr, undated; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 28)
      - Keating, Francis A. II, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 29)
      - Keene, David A, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 30)
      - Kelley, Paul X, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 31)
      - Kemp, Jack, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 32)
      - Kennedy, David M, 1985; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 33)
      - Kennickell, Ralph E. Jr, 1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 34)
      - Khedouri, Frederick N, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 35)
      - Kimmel, Joe Jr, 1985; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 36)
      - Kinard, John D, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 37)
      - Kohl, Helmut, 1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 38)
      - K Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 39)
      - Lawrence, Murray, 1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 40)
      - Lawson, Nigel, 1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 41)
      - Lehrman, Lewis E, 1985; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 42)
      - Le Maistre, Charles A, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 43)
      - Leuver, Robert, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 44)
      - Lewis, Tom, 1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 45)
      - Long, Russell B, 1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 46)
      - Longstreth, Bevis, 1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 47)
      - Love, Ben F, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 48)
      - Lovin, Vicki, 1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 49)
      - Lyng, Richard E, 1987; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 50)
      - L Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 51)
      - Maffitt, Peter C, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 52)
      - Mansfield, Mike, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 83, Folder 53)
      - Marcos, Ferdinand E, 1985; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Marr, R. Robert, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Martin, Missy, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Martin, William M, 1987; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Martina, D. F, 1987; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Mathias, Charles M. Jr, 1985; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - Matthews, William C, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - Maxwell, David O, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 8)
      - Mayo, Elaine, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 9)
      - McCullough, Andrew Dossett, 1985; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - McHenry, Adams C, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - McKevitt, James D, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - McLean, J. W, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 13)
      - McNamar, R. T, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 14)
      - Meese, Edwin III, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 15)
      - Michel, Robert H, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 16)
      - Miller, James C, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 17)
      - Mitchell, W. Eugene, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 18)
      - Miyazawa, Kiichi, 1988; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 19)
      - Moffitt, Bonner, 1985; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 20)
      - Mooers, Maria, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 21)
      - Moore, Preston, 1985-1988; 2 folders (Box 84, Folder 22-23)
      - Moore, Preston III, 1987; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 24)
      - Morrison, Bruce, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 25)
      - Mosbacher, Robert, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 26)
      - Moynihan, Daniel P, 1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 27)
      - Mulford, David C, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 28)
      - Mulroney, Brian, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 29)
      - Murkowski, Frank, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 30)
      - Murphy, Peter O, 1988; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 31)
      - Murtha, John P, 1987; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 32)
      - M Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 33)
      - Nakasone, Yasuhiro, 1987; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 34)
      - Newell, W. S, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 35)
      - Newton, Norman F, 1987; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 36)
      - Niehenke, John J, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 37)
      - Nixon, Richard M, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 84, Folder 38)
      - Nofziger, Lyn, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - N Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - O'Brien, George M. and Mary Lou, 1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - O'Connor, John J, 1985; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - O'Donnell, Peter Jr, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - O'Leary, Jeremiah, 1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - O Miscellaneous, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - Packwood, Bob, 1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - Parks, Fred, 1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 9)
      - Parr, Jerry S, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 10)
      - Paton, David, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 11)
      - Payne, Claude E, 1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 12)
      - Pearlman, Ronald A, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 13)
      - Poindexter, John M, 1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 14)
      - Polk, Louis F. Jr, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 15)
      - Porter, Roger B, 1985; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 16)
      - Pope, Donna, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 17)
      - Powell, Lewis F. Jr, 1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 18)
      - Pressler, Larry, 1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 19)
      - Priddy, Hervey A, 1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 20)
      - Proxmire, William, 1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 21)
      - P Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 22)
      - Q Miscellaneous, 1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 23)
      - Reagan, Nancy, 1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 24)
      - Reagan, Ronald, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 25)
      - Regan, Donald T, 1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 26)
      - Reynolds, Nancy Clark, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 27)
      - Ridings, Dorothy S, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 28)
      - Roberts, Paul Craig, 1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 29)
      - Rockefeller, Laurence, 1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 30)
      - Rostenkowski, Dan, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 31)
      - Roukema, Marge, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 32)
      - Roussel, Peter, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 33)
      - Rudd, Eldon, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 34)
      - Rush, R. Stockton, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 35)
      - R Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 36)
      - Schluter, Poul, 1985; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 37)
      - Seals, Woodrow, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 38)
      - Ser, Yvonne, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 39)
      - Shad, John, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 40)
      - Shanley, Bernard M, 1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 41)
      - Shultz, George P, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 42)
      - Simon, William E, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 43)
      - Simpson, John R, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 44)
      - Smart, S. Bruce Jr, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 45)
      - Smick, David, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 46)
      - Smyth, Catherine, 1983-1985; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 47)
      - Snyder, Bruce W, 1985; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 48)
      - Snyder, John W, 1985; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 49)
      - Speakes, Larry, 1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 50)
      - Stanton, J. William, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 51)
      - Stevens, Ted, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 52)
      - Stewart, Maco, 1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 53)
      - Stimpson, William H, 1985; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 54)
      - Strauss, Robert S, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 55)
      - Symms, Steve, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 85, Folder 56)
      - S Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Takeshita, Noboru, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Teeley, Peter B, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Thomas, H. Grant, 1985; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Thomspon, Jim, 1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Thomspon, Robert J, 1985; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - Thornburgh, Dick, 1985; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Thornhill, W. R, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Thurmond, Strom, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - Tisch, Preston R, 1986; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - Torczyner, Jacques, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - Tuttle, Robert H, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 12)
      - T Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 13)
      - Utsumi, Makoto, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 14)
      - U Miscellaneous, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 15)
      - Vander Jagt, Ginny, 1986; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 16)
      - Vander Jagt, Guy, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 17)
      - Verity, C. William, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 18)
      - Vetter, Edward O, 1986; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 19)
      - Vogelpohl, William George, 1987; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 20)
      - Volcker, Paul A, 1987; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 21)
      - V Miscellaneous, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 22)
      - Waldrip, Dibrell, 1987; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 23)
      - Wang, Bingqian, 1985; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 24)
      - Wanniski, Jude, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 25)
      - Warner, John W, undated; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 26)
      - Whetstone, Frank A, 1985; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 27)
      - Wilkins, C. Howard Jr, 1985; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 28)
      - Will, George F, 1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 29)
      - Wilson, John R, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 30)
      - Wilson, Margaret S, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 31)
      - Wilson, Michael H, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 32)
      - Wilson, Pete, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 33)
      - Winston, Will T, 1985; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 34)
      - Wortley, George C, undated; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 35)
      - Wylie, Chalmers P, 1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 36)
      - W Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 37)
      - Xiannian, Li, 1985; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 38)
      - Xu, Han, 1985; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 39)
      - Yilin, Yao, 1986; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 40)
      - Young, Hubert H. Jr, 1985-1986; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 41)
      - Y Miscellaneous, 1986; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 42)
      - Zachs, Gordon, 1987; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 43)
      - Zoellick, Robert B, 1988; 1 folder (Box 86, Folder 44)
    - Personal Chronological Files, 1985-1988; 2 boxes
      - 1985-1986, 6 folders (Box 87, Folder 1-6)
      - 1987-1988, 4 folders (Box 88, Folder 1-4)
  - Subseries 7D. Gift Reports, 1985-1988; 2 boxes
    Gift reports include information about the frequent gifts Baker received from representatives of foreign governments and various organizations and corporations, as well as other individuals. The majority of the gifts are of little monetary value.
    - 1985-1988, 2 folders (Box 88, Folder 5-6)
    - 1985-1988, 9 folders (Box 89, Folder 1-9)
  - Subseries 7E. Memoranda and Notes, 1985-1988; 1 box
    The Memoranda and Notes subseries includes only a few folders of notes (sometimes handwritten) and miscellaneous memoranda related to tax reform and other topics.
    - General, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Tax Reform, 1985; 1 folder (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 7F. Scheduling, 1985-1988; 7 boxes
    The scheduling materials document the extensive planning and careful arrangement of Baker's days and include daily schedules as well as diaries, long-range schedule planning, and scenarios, or intricately plotted procedures for public appearances, trips, and meetings.
    The daily schedules document Baker's daily activities, including meetings and engagements, meals, travel, and personal time. Daily schedules from 1985 through 1987 have been recreated from Treasury schedules after the originals were inadvertently destroyed (see memo at the front of each binder for details), and are not reflective of changes that may have occurred during the course of the day. Also included in this grouping are original schedules from 1988 which contain detailed daily schedules and handwritten updates, in addition to a small amount of correspondence and other documents.
    The scenarios consist of comprehensive schedules for specific events and trips, and in addition to schedules include detailed instructions for Baker on such subjects as appropriate dress, weather forecasts, flight manifests, seating information, and relevant contact information.
    The travel logs include additional schedules and scenarios, but also include information on travel related to appearances on behalf of various political candidates, in addition to trips taken in conjunction with Treasury Department business.
    The long-range invitations consist of scheduling requests made to Baker one to three months in advance of events.
    The diaries contain daily scheduling information, some of which repeats information found in the daily schedules grouping, but which is largely dedicated to personal or non-official obligations.
    The subseries is arranged alphabetically. Each type of scheduling information is arranged chronologically.
    - Daily Schedules, 1985-1987; 5 folders (Box 90, Folder 3-7)
    - Daily Schedules (continued), 1988; 3 folders (Box 91, Folder 1-3)
    - Diaries, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 91, Folder 4-5)
    - Diaries, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 92, Folder 1-2)
    - Long Range Invitations and Scheduling, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 92, Folder 3-4)
    - Long Range Invitations and Scheduling (continued), 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
    - Scenarios, 1985-1986 May; 4 folders (Box 93, Folder 3-6)
    - Scenarios (continued), 1986 June-1988 April; 7 folders (Box 94, Folder 1-7)
    - Scenarios (continued), 1988 May-1988 (1 Folder), 1 folder (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Travel Logs, 1985 March-1987 October; 6 folders (Box 95, Folder 2-7)
    - Travel Logs (continued), 1987 November-1988 August (1 Folder), 1 folder (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 7G. Subject Files, 1983-1988; 3 boxes